instantwatcher.com 2016-06-08

# Privacy Policy - instantwatcher.com - Netflix US - instantwatcher

### Privacy Policy for InstantWatcher.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [info@kajasoftware.com](mailto:info@kajasoftware.com).

At InstantWatcher.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by [instantwatcher.com](http://instantwatcher.com/) and how it is used.

#### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, InstantWatcher.com utilizes log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are NOT linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

InstantWatcher.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

We do use cookies to store information, such as your username if you are logged in. We also use third party advertisements on InstantWatcher.com. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

#### DoubleClick (Google) DART Cookie

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google's DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/?hl=en). 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [instantwatcher.com](http://instantwatcher.com/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. InstantWatcher.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into your account or seamlessly playing back a Netflix movie title.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

#### External Links

By visiting the external links shown in Link page of this site, visitors are stipulated with the Privacy Policy and Terms of Services of respective web sites they visits.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [info@kajasoftware.com](mailto:info@kajasoftware.com)
